(this["webpackJsonpreact-quiz-app"]=this["webpackJsonpreact-quiz-app"]||[]).push([[3],{36:function(e,a,t){"use strict";t.d(a,"a",(function(){return n}));var s=t(37);function n(e,a){if(e){if("string"===typeof e)return Object(s.a)(e,a);var t=Object.prototype.toString.call(e).slice(8,-1);return"Object"===t&&e.constructor&&(t=e.constructor.name),"Map"===t||"Set"===t?Array.from(e):"Arguments"===t||/^(?:Ui|I)nt(?:8|16|32)(?:Clamped)?Array$/.test(t)?Object(s.a)(e,a):void 0}}},37:function(e,a,t){"use strict";function s(e,a){(null==a||a>e.length)&&(a=e.length);for(var t=0,s=new Array(a);t<a;t++)s[t]=e[t];return s}t.d(a,"a",(function(){return s}))},38:function(e,a,t){"use strict";t.d(a,"a",(function(){return n}));var s=t(36);function n(e,a){return function(e){if(Array.isArray(e))return e}(e)||function(e,a){if("undefined"!==typeof Symbol&&Symbol.iterator in Object(e)){var t=[],s=!0,n=!1,r=void 0;try{for(var c,i=e[Symbol.iterator]();!(s=(c=i.next()).done)&&(t.push(c.value),!a||t.length!==a);s=!0);}catch(l){n=!0,r=l}finally{try{s||null==i.return||i.return()}finally{if(n)throw r}}return t}}(e,a)||Object(s.a)(e,a)||function(){throw new TypeError("Invalid attempt to destructure non-iterable instance.\nIn order to be iterable, non-array objects must have a [Symbol.iterator]() method.")}()}},39:function(e,a,t){"use strict";t.d(a,"c",(function(){return s})),t.d(a,"b",(function(){return n})),t.d(a,"a",(function(){return r}));var s=[{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"0990996"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"093909"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"009039"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"090089"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"01010101"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"092299"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"986709999"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"222099EAS"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"2222099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"09922099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"222292099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"0998999099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"09909999343"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"09909999999999"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"0990999999943"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"09459099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"0912219099"}],n=function(){var e=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:5;return Promise.resolve(s.sort((function(){return.5-Math.random()})).slice(0,e))},r=Object.freeze([{_id:"5c8a1d5b0190b214360dc057",name:"Jonas Schmedtmann",email:"admin@example.com",role:"admin",password:"123456"},{_id:"5c8a1dfa2f8fb814b56fa181",name:"Lourdes Browning",email:"loulou@example.com",role:"user",password:"123456"},{_id:"5c8a1e1a2f8fb814b56fa182",name:"Sophie Louise Hart",email:"sophie@example.com",role:"user",password:"123456"}])},40:function(e,a,t){"use strict";var s=t(1);t(0);a.a=function(e){var a=e.message,t=e.alertClassType;return Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"alert alert-dismissible fade show ".concat(t),role:"alert",children:[a,Object(s.jsx)("button",{type:"button",className:"btn-close","data-bs-dismiss":"alert","aria-label":"Close"})]})}},41:function(e,a,t){"use strict";t.d(a,"a",(function(){return r}));var s=t(37);var n=t(36);function r(e){return function(e){if(Array.isArray(e))return Object(s.a)(e)}(e)||function(e){if("undefined"!==typeof Symbol&&Symbol.iterator in Object(e))return Array.from(e)}(e)||Object(n.a)(e)||function(){throw new TypeError("Invalid attempt to spread non-iterable instance.\nIn order to be iterable, non-array objects must have a [Symbol.iterator]() method.")}()}},42:function(e,a,t){"use strict";var s=t(1),n=t(0),r=t(38),c=t(2),i=t(9),l=t(11),o=function(){var e=Object(c.g)(),a=Object(n.useState)({}),t=Object(r.a)(a,2),o=t[0],d=t[1];Object(n.useEffect)((function(){var e=Object(l.b)("authUserInfo")?Object(l.b)("authUserInfo"):{};d(e)}),[]);return Object(s.jsx)("nav",{className:"navbar navbar-expand-lg navbar-light bg-light",children:Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"container-fluid",children:[Object(s.jsx)("a",{className:"navbar-brand",href:"#",children:"Quiz App"}),Object(s.jsx)("button",{className:"navbar-toggler",type:"button","data-bs-toggle":"collapse","data-bs-target":"#navbarSupportedContent","aria-controls":"navbarSupportedContent","aria-expanded":"false","aria-label":"Toggle navigation",children:Object(s.jsx)("span",{className:"navbar-toggler-icon"})}),Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"collapse navbar-collapse",id:"navbarSupportedContent",children:[Object(s.jsxs)("ul",{className:"navbar-nav mx-auto mb-2 mb-lg-0",children:[Object(s.jsx)("li",{className:"nav-item",children:Object(s.jsx)(i.c,{activeClassName:"active",className:"nav-link",to:"/questions",children:"Question"})}),o&&Object.keys(o).length>0&&"user"===o.role?Object(s.jsx)("li",{className:"nav-item",children:Object(s.jsx)(i.c,{activeClassName:"active",className:"nav-link",to:"/user/answer",children:"Answer"})}):null,o&&Object.keys(o).length>0&&"admin"===o.role?Object(s.jsxs)(s.Fragment,{children:[Object(s.jsx)("li",{className:"nav-item",children:Object(s.jsx)(i.c,{activeClassName:"active",className:"nav-link",to:"/admin/answer",children:"Answer"})}),Object(s.jsx)("li",{className:"nav-item",children:Object(s.jsx)(i.c,{activeClassName:"active",className:"nav-link",to:"/admin/quiz",children:"Quiz"})})]}):null]}),Object(s.jsx)("div",{className:"d-flex align-items-center",children:o&&Object.keys(o).length>0?Object(s.jsxs)(s.Fragment,{children:[Object(s.jsx)("span",{children:o.name}),Object(s.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){Object(l.a)(),e.push("/")},className:"ms-3 btn btn-outline-primary",children:"Logout"})]}):Object(s.jsx)(i.b,{role:"button",className:"btn btn-outline-success",to:"/",children:"SignIn"})})]})]})})};a.a=function(e){var a=e.children;return Object(s.jsxs)(s.Fragment,{children:[Object(s.jsx)(o,{}),Object(s.jsx)("main",{role:"main",className:" container mt-4",children:a})]})}},45:function(e,a,t){"use strict";t.r(a);var s=t(1),n=t(41),r=t(17),c=t(7),i=t(38),l=t(0),o=t(42),d=t(40),b=t(39),u=t(11);a.default=function(){var e=Object(l.useState)({}),a=Object(i.a)(e,2),t=(a[0],a[1]),j=Object(l.useState)(b.c),h=Object(i.a)(j,2),m=h[0],v=h[1],O=Object(l.useState)({}),p=Object(i.a)(O,2),x=p[0],f=p[1],w=Object(l.useState)({question:"",answer1:"",answer2:"",answer3:"",answer4:"",correct:""}),y=Object(i.a)(w,2),N=y[0],k=y[1],g=Object(l.useState)(),q=Object(i.a)(g,2),I=q[0],C=q[1];Object(l.useEffect)((function(){var e=Object(u.b)("authUserInfo")?Object(u.b)("authUserInfo"):{};t(e)}),[]);var S=function(e){var a=e.target;k(Object(c.a)(Object(c.a)({},N),{},Object(r.a)({},a.name,a.value)))};return Object(s.jsxs)(o.a,{children:[Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"row",children:[Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:" d-flex justify-content-between mb-3",children:[Object(s.jsx)("h5",{children:" Quiz "}),Object(s.jsx)("button",{className:"btn btn-primary","data-bs-toggle":"modal","data-bs-target":"#addQuizModal",children:"Add Quiz"})]}),Object(s.jsx)("div",{className:"table-responsive",children:Object(s.jsxs)("table",{className:"table table-striped align-middle table-hover",children:[Object(s.jsx)("thead",{children:Object(s.jsxs)("tr",{children:[Object(s.jsx)("th",{scope:"col",children:"QuestionId"}),Object(s.jsx)("th",{scope:"col",children:"Question"}),Object(s.jsx)("th",{scope:"col",children:"Answers"}),Object(s.jsx)("th",{scope:"col",children:"Correct"}),Object(s.jsx)("th",{scope:"col",children:"Action"})]})}),Object(s.jsx)("tbody",{children:m&&m.length>0?m.map((function(e,a){return Object(s.jsxs)("tr",{kay:e.questionId,children:[Object(s.jsx)("td",{children:e.questionId}),Object(s.jsx)("td",{children:e.question}),Object(s.jsx)("td",{children:e.answers.map((function(e){return Object(s.jsx)(s.Fragment,{children:e})}))}),Object(s.jsx)("td",{children:e.correct}),Object(s.jsxs)("td",{children:[Object(s.jsx)("button",{"data-bs-toggle":"modal","data-bs-target":"#updateModal",onClick:function(){return function(e){f(e)}(e)},className:"btn text-warning",children:Object(s.jsx)("i",{className:"bi bi-pencil-square"})}),Object(s.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){},className:"btn text-danger",children:Object(s.jsx)("i",{className:"bi bi-trash-fill"})})]})]})})):Object(s.jsx)("tr",{children:Object(s.jsx)("td",{colSpan:"6",children:"Data not found "})})})]})})]}),Object(s.jsx)("div",{className:"modal fade",id:"addQuizModal",tabIndex:"-1","aria-labelledby":"addQuizModalLabel","aria-hidden":"true",children:Object(s.jsx)("div",{className:"modal-dialog modal-dialog-centered modal-dialog-scrollable",children:Object(s.jsx)("div",{className:"modal-content",children:Object(s.jsxs)("form",{onSubmit:function(e){e.preventDefault();var a={question:"",answers:[],correct:"",questionId:Math.floor(9999*Math.random()+1)},t=Object.keys(N).sort().reduce((function(e,a){return e[a]=N[a],e}),{});if(Object.values(t).length>0)for(var s in t)Object.hasOwnProperty.call(t,s)&&("answer1"!==s&&"answer2"!==s&&"answer3"!==s&&"answer4"!==s||a.answers.push(t[s]),"question"===s&&(a.question=t[s]),"correct"===s&&(a.correct=t[s]));Object(u.c)("tempQuiz",[].concat(Object(n.a)(m),[a])),k({question:"",answer1:"",answer2:"",answer3:"",answer4:"",correct:""}),v([].concat(Object(n.a)(m),[a])),C("Quiz add successful!")},children:[Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"modal-header",children:[Object(s.jsx)("h5",{className:"modal-title",id:"addQuizModalLabel",children:"Quiz"}),Object(s.jsx)("button",{type:"button",className:"btn-close","data-bs-dismiss":"modal","aria-label":"Close",onClick:function(){C("")}})]}),Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"modal-body",children:[I&&I?Object(s.jsx)(d.a,{message:I,alertClassType:"alert-success"}):null,Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"mb-3",children:[Object(s.jsx)("label",{htmlFor:"question",className:"form-label",children:"Question"}),Object(s.jsx)("input",{type:"text",className:"form-control",id:"question",name:"question",placeholder:"Question",value:N.question,onChange:S,required:!0})]}),Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"mb-3 row",children:[Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"col",children:[Object(s.jsx)("label",{htmlFor:"question",className:"form-label",children:"Answer 1"}),Object(s.jsx)("input",{type:"text",className:"form-control",id:"answer2",name:"answer1",placeholder:"Answer 1",value:N.answer1,onChange:S,required:!0})]}),Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"col",children:[Object(s.jsx)("label",{htmlFor:"question",className:"form-label",children:"Answer 2"}),Object(s.jsx)("input",{type:"text",className:"form-control",id:"answer2",name:"answer2",placeholder:"Answer 2",value:N.answer2,onChange:S,required:!0})]})]}),Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"mb-3 row",children:[Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"col",children:[Object(s.jsx)("label",{htmlFor:"question",className:"form-label",children:"Answer 3"}),Object(s.jsx)("input",{type:"text",className:"form-control",id:"answer3",name:"answer3",placeholder:"Answer 3",value:N.answer3,onChange:S,required:!0})]}),Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"col",children:[Object(s.jsx)("label",{htmlFor:"question",className:"form-label",children:"Answer 4"}),Object(s.jsx)("input",{type:"text",className:"form-control",id:"answer4",name:"answer4",placeholder:"Answer4",value:N.answer4,onChange:S,required:!0})]})]}),Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"mb-3",children:[Object(s.jsx)("label",{htmlFor:"correct",className:"form-label",children:"Correct"}),Object(s.jsx)("input",{type:"text",className:"form-control",id:"correct",name:"correct",placeholder:"Correct",value:N.correct,onChange:S,required:!0})]})]}),Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"modal-footer",children:[Object(s.jsx)("button",{type:"button",className:"btn btn-secondary","data-bs-dismiss":"modal",children:"Close"}),Object(s.jsx)("button",{type:"submit",className:"btn btn-primary",children:"Save"})]})]})})})}),Object(s.jsx)("div",{className:"modal fade",id:"updateModal",tabIndex:"-1","aria-labelledby":"updateModalLabel","aria-hidden":"true",children:Object(s.jsx)("div",{className:"modal-dialog modal-dialog-centered modal-dialog-scrollable",children:Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"modal-content",children:[Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"modal-header",children:[Object(s.jsx)("h5",{className:"modal-title",id:"updateModalLabel",children:"Quiz update"}),Object(s.jsx)("button",{type:"button",className:"btn-close","data-bs-dismiss":"modal","aria-label":"Close"})]}),Object(s.jsx)("div",{className:"modal-body",children:x&&x?Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"card",children:[Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"card-body",children:[Object(s.jsxs)("h5",{className:"card-title",children:["Question: ",x.question]}),Object(s.jsxs)("h6",{className:"card-subtitle mb-2 text-muted",children:["Question Id: ",x.questionId]}),Object(s.jsxs)("p",{className:"card-text text-success",children:["Correct: ",x.correct]})]}),Object(s.jsx)("ul",{className:"list-group list-group-flush",children:x.answers&&x.answers.map((function(e,a){return Object(s.jsxs)("li",{className:"list-group-item",children:["Answer ",a," : ",e]},a+1)}))})]}):null}),Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"modal-footer",children:[Object(s.jsx)("button",{type:"button",className:"btn btn-secondary","data-bs-dismiss":"modal",children:"Close"}),Object(s.jsx)("button",{type:"button",className:"btn btn-primary",children:"Save changes"})]})]})})})]})}}}]);
//# sourceMappingURL=3.ecfd9184.chunk.js.map